Apple has hit an extraordinary milestone
it is the first trillion-dollar publicly
traded corporation in American history
the company was valued at one trillion 1
billion six hundred seventy nine million
two hundred twenty thousand dollars but
who's counting we need a blue screen
when Wall Street closed yesterday you
probably know the names of Apple's
founders Steve Jobs and Steve Wozniak
and the current CEO Tim Cook but you
might not know Ronald Wayne Wayne is one
of Apple's original founders who sold
his 10% stake in the 1970s after just 12
days for 800 dollars that is correct 800
dollars today those same shares would be
worth 100 billion did you have any doubt
that Apple would be a successful company
none I was it was the right product at
the right time so why did you sell out
my passion wasn't computers in the first
place it was slot machines I also knew
that I was standing in the shadow of
giants and as a result I knew I was
never going to have a product of my own
to develop you can see more of John
Blackstone's interview with Ronald Wayne
tonight on the CBS Evening News with
Jeff Glor I'm interested in knowing more
about psychology if they just kept ten
shares even I don't understand why you'd
sell the whole thing you know just keep
a couple they'll be worth 50 billion in
a couple decades